Jason Worley

234 Pulaski St, Brooklyn, NY 11206, USA Brooklyn, NY, 11206 (718) 772-2732 jjasonworleyy@gmail.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Adaptable recent college graduate with a Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) in Philosophy (3.6 GPA), with 7+ years of work experience. Aiming to leverage academic experience and a proven knowledge of account development, client relations, and campaign management to successfully fill the Marketing Assistant role at your company. Frequently praised as efficient by my peers, I can be relied upon to help your company achieve its goals.

EDUCATION

Hunter College New York, NY B.A. Philosophy (May 2019)

• **GPA:** 3.6

• Award And Honor: Phi Sigma Tau International Honor Society for Philosophy

WORK EXPERIENCE

LE BARRICOU, Brooklyn, NY

Server, May 2017 - Present

- Serve food or beverages to patrons, and prepare or serve specialty dishes at tables as required.
- Explain how various menu items are prepared, describing ingredients and cooking methods.
- Bring wine selections to tables with appropriate glasses, and pour the wines for customers.
- Present menus to patrons and answer questions about menu items, making recommendations upon request.

VILLAGE VOICE, New York, NY

Account Sales Rep, Aug 2012 - Sep 2014

- Maintain assigned account bases while developing new accounts.
- Explain to customers how specific types of advertising will help promote their products or services in the most effective way possible.
- Process all correspondence and paperwork related to accounts.
- Prepare and deliver sales presentations to new and existing customers to sell new advertising programs, and to protect and increase existing advertising.
- Write copy as part of layout.
- Gather all relevant material for bid processes, and coordinate bidding and contract approval.

FORT WORTH WEEKLY NEWSPAPER, Fort Worth, TX

Inside Sales Account Executive, Sep 2009 – Jun 2012

- Maintain assigned account bases while developing new accounts.
- Locate and contact potential clients to offer advertising services.
- Prepare and deliver sales presentations to new and existing customers to sell new advertising programs, and to protect and increase existing advertising.
- Prepare promotional plans, sales literature, media kits, and sales contracts, using computer.

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Microsoft Suite Proficient
- Excel Proficient